Guide to the Chiapas Media Project Records TAM.774
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series I. Video Archive, 1995-2009; 3.5 Linear Feet in 1 record carton, 1 manuscript box, and 5 cassette boxes; 224 MiniDV; 25 VHS; 1 audiocassette; 1 Betacam_SP; 2 DVCAM; 1 DVDs
  - Sub-Series 1.D: Living Juarez, 1998-2009
    - Promocion del PMC, Ojo de Agua Communication, Undated (Box 21, Minidv 774_168, 774_169)
    - Quiere Decir Que No Vamos a Pasar?, 2007 (Box 21, Minidv 774_170, 774_207)
    - Reclaiming Justice: Guerrero's Indigenous Community Police, 2002 (Box 21, Minidv 774_171, 774_172)
    - Reclaiming Justice: Guerrero's Indigenous Community Police Licensing Contract - Maori TV, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - La Resistencia, 2001 (Box 20, Minidv 774_150, 774_151)
    - San Chris. 2, October, 2009 (Box 21, Minidv 774_173)
    - El Silencio de los Zapatistas (The Silence of the Zapatistas), 2001 (Box 20, Minidv 774_132, Box 21, Minidv 774_188)
    - Son de la Tierra (Song of the Earth), 2002-2003 (Box 21, Minidv 774_174, 774_175, 774_176, 774_177, 774_178)
    - The Strength of the Indigenous People of Mut-Vitz, 2000 (Box 21, Minidv 774_179, 774_180)
    - The Strength of the Indigenous People of Mut Vitz Licensing Contract, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - La Tierra Es De Quien La Trabaja (The Land Belongs to Those Who Work It, 2006 (Box 20, Minidv 774_152, Box 21, Minidv 774_183)
    - La Tierra Es De Quien La Trabaja (The Land Belongs to Those Who Work It Spanish and English Transcripts, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - La Tierra Sagrada (The Sacred Land), 2000 (Box 20, Minidv 774_153, Box 21, Minidv 774_186, 774_187)
      Camera: Franklin Quizhpe
    - Toxic Waste in Parago Territory, 2007 (Box 21, Minidv 774_191)
    - Trabajos Colectivos en Resistencia, 2000 (Box 21, Minidv 774_192)
    - Videos de los Altos, 1999 (Box 21, Minidv 774_193)
    - Villas De S. Confront. Feds y Julian, October, 2009 (Box 21, Minidv 774_194)
    - La Vida de la Mujer en Resistencia (The Life of the Woman in Resistance), 2005 (Box 20, Minidv 774_154, Box 21, Minidv 774_184)
    - Viva la Vida, Muera la Muerte, 2003-2010 (Box 21, Minidv 774_195)
    - Viva la Vida, Muera la Muerte Spanish Transcript, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Volver Vivir #6, October, 2009 (Box 21, Minidv 774_196)
    - Walking Towards the Dawn, 2002 (Box 21, Minidv 774_197, 774_198)
    - Water and Autonomy, 2003 (Box 21, Minidv 774_199)
    - We Are Equal: Zapatista Women Speak, 2004 (Box 21, Minidv 774_200, 774_201, Box 22, Minidv 774_225)
    - We Are Equal: Zapatista Women Speak English and Spanish Transcripts, Undated (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - The WTO: A Threat to Humanity, 2003 (Box 21, Minidv 774_189, 774_190)
    - Xulum' Chon: Weavers in Resistance from the Highlands, 2002 (Box 21, Minidv 774_205, 774_206)
  - Sub-Series 1.E: TV Serrana, 1996-2010
    This Sub-Series contains video interviews with Cuban filmmakers conducted by Alexandra Halkin.
    - Carlitos Pedro Luis, 2010 (Box 21, Minidv 774_212)
    - Deflin Gomez, Ariagna, Lenia, 2010 (Box 21, Minidv 774_213)
    - Interview Rigo, Undated (Box 21, Minidv 774_214)
    - Mandela in Cuba, June 17, 1996 (Box 23, Betacam sp 774_228)
    - San Pablo Interviews 1, 2010 (Box 21, Minidv 774_215)
    - San Pablo Interviews 2, Undated (Box 21, Minidv 774_216)
  - Sub-Series 1.F: Zapatista Communities, 1995-2007
    This Sub-Series contains video interviews with members of Zapatista communities, recordings of video workshops, depictions of daily life, and other video documentaries related to the Zapatista movement.
    - Aborto Sin Pena, 2005 (Box 23, Dvd 774_233)
    - Acteal Estrategia de Muerte, Undated (Box 23, Vhs 774_234)
    - Caminando Hacia El Amanecer, 2002 (Box 21, Minidv 774_217)
    - Camino de la Nueva Salud, 2007 (Box 21, Minidv 774_218)
    - Chiapas; the fights for land and liberty, 1994 (Box 23, Vhs 774_236)
    - Chiapas Media Project y la Familia Indigena (Chaipas Media Project and the Indigenous Family) -- English Version, 1998; cuid45279 (Box Shared Tamiment 207, Dvcam cuid45279)
    - Chiapas Media Project y la Familia Indigena (Chaipas Media Project and the Indigenous Family) -- Spanish Version, April, 1998; cuid45280 (Box Shared Tamiment 207, Dvcam cuid45280)
    - Chiapas Nunca Mas, Undated (Box 23, Vhs 774_235)
    - Chiapas -- Student Videos, August, 1998; cuid45275 (Box 24, Hi8 cuid45275)
    - Chiapas Youth Media Project 1 -- Morelia, February, 1998; cuid45276 (Box 24, Hi8 cuid45276)
    - Chiapas Youth Media Project 2 -- Morelia, February, 1998; cuid45277 (Box 24, Hi8 cuid45277)
    - Chiapas Youth Media Project 3 -- Morelia, 1998; cuid45249 (Box 24, Hi8 cuid45249)
    - Computer Workshops Men and Women -- Francisco Gomez, November, 1998; cuid45257 (Box 24, Hi8 cuid45257)
    - Consulta -- Master Compilation 1, November, 1998; cuid45255 (Box 24, Hi8 cuid45255)
    - Consulta -- Master Compilation 2, November, 1998; cuid45256 (Box 24, Hi8 cuid45256)
    - The Damned from the War in Chiapas, Undated (Box 23, Vhs 774_252)
      May be an access copy of Andrea Chávez Peón's 1998 Damnificados de la guerra en Chiapas
    - Delegation Performance -- Egido Morelia, December, 1998; cuid45258 (Box 24, Hi8 cuid45258)
    - Desplazados por la violencia politica: Chenalho Chiapas Mexcio, 1998; Cracked VHS cartridge repaired in June, 2022 (Box 23, Vhs 774_237)
      Created by Carlos Martinez Suarez
    - Edigo Morelia -- New Years '99, December, 1998; cuid45260 (Box 24, Hi8 cuid45260)
    - Egido Morelia -- Women's Video Workshop, January, 1999; cuid45265 (Box 24, Hi8 cuid45265)
    - El Efecto del Tequila, 1995 (Box 23, Vhs 774_238)
      Created by Gloria Ribé and José Manuel Pintado
    - El Ejido Prado Pacayal: violaciones los derechos humanos en Chiapas, 1995 (Box 23, Vhs 774_239)
    - El Ejido Prado Pacayal: violaciones los derechos humanos en Chiapas Video Insert (774_239), 1995 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Entrega de Cadaueres en la comunidad union progreso municipio San Juan de la Libertad, Chiapas, Undated (Box 23, Vhs 774_242)
    - Entrevista al Subcomandante Marcos, 1994 (Box 23, Vhs 774_243)
    - Gallardo 1, March 22, 2010 (Box 22, Minidv 774_219)
    - Gallardo 2, March 22, 2010 (Box 22, Minidv 774_220)
    - Guerrilla Video Primer: Learn how to tape, edit, and distribute videos for radical social change, 2002 (Box 23, Vhs 774_244)
      Created by the Cascadia Media Collective
    - Guerrilla Video Primer Cascadia Media Collective Insert (774_244), 2002 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Interview -- Pedro Garruda, Francisco Gomez, undated; cuid45266 (Box 24, Hi8 cuid45266)
    - Interview for Toronto -- Francisco Gomez, March, 1999; cuid45272 (Box 24, Hi8 cuid45272)
    - The Invisible War - Grant Paperwork, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Lacandona: The Zapatistas and Rainforest of Chiapas, Mexico, 1998 (Box 23, Vhs 774_245)
      Created by Native Forest Network, Eastern North American Resource Center
    - Marcos' Message to Freeing the Media, Undated (Box 23, Vhs 774_246)
      Created by Paper Tiger TV
    - Memorias de San Andres, Undated (Box 23, Vhs 774_247)
    - Militares ocupan el campamento de refugiados en X'oyep: Chenalho Chiapas Mexico, 1998 (Box 23, Vhs 774_248)
    - Mision de Paz y Derechos en Chiapas: Entrevista con el Subcomandante Marcos, 1994 (Box 23, Vhs 774_249)
    - Morelia -- Old Videos, undated; cuid45281 (Box Shared Tamiment 207, Dvcam cuid45281)
    - Morelia y Oventic -- Interviews, May, 1998; cuid45254 (Box 24, Hi8 cuid45254)
    - Pro-TV Work Sample, Undated (Box 23, Vhs 774_250)
      Created by Downtown Community TV Center
    - La Realidad -- Camera Workshops, May, 1998; cuid45252 (Box 24, Hi8 cuid45252)
    - La Realidad -- Interviews, May, 1998; cuid45251 (Box 24, Hi8 cuid45251)
    - La Realidad -- Student Tapes, May, 1998; cuid45253 (Box 24, Hi8 cuid45253)
    - Revolution in San Cristobal, Undated (Box 23, Vhs 774_251)
    - Roberto Barrios -- Student Interviews, 1999; cuid45271 (Box 24, Hi8 cuid45271)
    - Roberto Barrios -- Student Work, undated; cuid45273 (Box 24, Hi8 cuid45273)
    - Student Workshop -- Francisco Gomez, 1998; cuid45274 (Box 24, Hi8 cuid45274)
    - El Sueno Zapatista; Cinco anos despues, Undated (Box 23, Vhs 774_240, 774_241)
    - Tour '99, 1999 (Box 22, Minidv 774_221)
    - Tour '99, April, 1999; cuid45278 (Box 24, Dvcam cuid45278)
    - Tour '99 Licensing Contract, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Unlabeled Tape, Undated (Box 22, Minidv 774_222)
    - Unlabeled Tape, Undated (Box 22, Minidv 774_223)
    - Video Revista Mecapal, 2004 (Box 22, Minidv 774_224)
    - Video Testimonio-Counter-Insurgency, 1996 (Box 23, Vhs 774_253)
      Created by Yolanda Rocio Reza Astudillo
    - Women's Video, November, 1998; cuid45259 (Box 24, Hi8 cuid45259)
    - Workshop La Garrucha -- Interviews, August, 1998; cuid45250 (Box 24, Hi8 cuid45250)
    - Workshops -- Francisco Gomez, August, 1998; cuid45264 (Box 24, Hi8 cuid45264)
    - Zapatistas, Cronica de una Reblion, Undated (Box 23, Vhs 774_254)
  - Sub-Series 1.G: La Mala Cosecha (The Bad Harvest), 1999
    La Mala Cosecha (The Bad Harvest) is a collaboration between indigenous and non-indigenous videomakers that documents severe food shortages in 1998, caused by natural disaster, extreme poverty, and military brutality. These videotapes contain source material for the 15 minute film, which was produced in 1999.
    - La Mala Cosecha (The Bad Harvest), 1999; cuid45282 (Box Shared Tamiment 207, Dvcam cuid45282)
    - Tape 1 -- Roberto Barrios, 1999; cuid45267 (Box 24, Hi8 cuid45267)
    - Tape 2 -- Roberto Barrios, 1999; cuid45268 (Box 24, Hi8 cuid45268)
    - Tape 3 -- Roberto Barrios, 1999; cuid45269 (Box 24, Hi8 cuid45269)
    - Tape 4 -- Roberto Barrios, 1999; cuid45270 (Box 24, Hi8 cuid45270)
    - Tape 5 -- Roberto Barrios Rice Harvest, January, 1999; cuid45261 (Box 24, Hi8 cuid45261)
    - Tape 6 -- Roberto Barrios Communal Gardens, January, 1999; cuid45262 (Box 24, Hi8 cuid45262)
    - Tape 8 -- Roberto Barrios, January, 1999; cuid45263 (Box 24, Hi8 cuid45263)
  - Free Speech TV -- Licensing Contracts, 2001-2003 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Video Covers and Sleeves, 1995-2002; cuid36493
    - Paper Documents (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Electronic Records, TW_TAM_774_ER_4
  - Video Sales Reports, Notes, and Related Correspondence, 2001-2010 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Videotape Order Invoices, 1999-2001 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Videotape Order Invoices, 2003-2005 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Videotape Order Invoices, 2004 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Videotape Order Invoices and Receipts, 2004 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Videotapes Sent Log, 2003-2004 (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Series II. Film Festivals and Screenings, 1997-2010; 3 Linear Feet in 5 manuscript boxes and 1 flat box
  This Series contains ephemera and documentation from film festivals, including catalogs, calendars, programs, posters, awards, visitor passes, planning documentation, and email correspondence.
  - African Diaspora Film Festival, New York City, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - African Diaspora Film Festival - Schedule, Anthology Film Archives, NY, 2002 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Alternative Media Festival, Indianapolis, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Arizona Film Festival, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Arizona International Film Festival, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Arizona International Film Festival - Programs, 2002-2003 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Arizona Independent Film Festival - Screening Announcement, Tucson Citizen, April 19, 2001 (Box Shared Tamiment 069, Folder 15)
  - Avanca International Meeting of Cinema, TV, Video and Multimedia, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Beeld Voor Beeld Festival Voor Visuele Antropologie, Amsterdam, 2002-2005 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Berks Filmmakers Screening Poster, Reading PA, 2006 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Big Muddy Film Festival, Carbondale, Illinois, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Big Muddy Film Festival, Southern Illinois University - Poster, February 20-29, 2004 (Box Shared Tamiment 069, Folder 16)
  - Casa de América Festival, Madrid, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - "Chiapas by the Chiapanecos" Screening Flyer, circa 2000 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Chiapas Media Project 10th Anniversary Tour - Event Poster, Addison Road Community Centre, Marrickville, Australia, April 12, 2008 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Chiapas Media Project Austin Tour Flyer, circa 2000 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Chiapas Media Project Film Festival, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Chiapas Media Project Tour Posters, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Chicago Latino Film Festival, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Cine Invisible: Festival Internacional Filme Sozialak, Bilbao, 2010 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Cine las Americas International Film Festival, Austin, circa 2006 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - CineEco: Festival Internacional de Cinema e Vídeo de Ambiente da Serra da Estrela, Portugal, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Cinema Texas International Short Film Festival, Austin, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - "Concierto En Solidaridad con Atenco" - Screening Poster, Navalquejigo, Spain, November 4, 2006 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence regarding festival submissions, 2001-2004 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - DC Independent Film Festival, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Defending the Forests (Defender los Bosques) Screening Advertisement, Chilpancingo, Guerrero, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Defending the Forests (Defender los Bosques) Screening Flyer, Tempe, Arizona, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Doc Aviv: Tel Aviv Documentary Film Festival, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Downtown Community TV Center Screening Flyers, New York, NY, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Dreamspeakers Film Festival, Alberta, Canada, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - EarthVision Environmental Film and Video Festival - Award, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Encuentro de Documentalistas, San Antonio, 2010 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Encuentro Hispanoamericano del Milenio de Video Documental Independiente, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Festival Americano de Cine y Video de los Pueblos Indígenas, Bolivia, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Festival Americano de Cine y Video de los Pueblos Indígenas, Guatemala, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Festival Awards, 2004-2009 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Festival ¡Cine Latino!, San Francisco, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Festival de Cine y Video de Pueblos Indígenas Americanos, Bolivia, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Festival de Cinéma - Screening Poster, Le Télégramme, Douarnenez, France, August, 2002 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Festival and Conference Badges, circa 2000-2010 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Festival Continental de Cine y Video de las Primeras Naciones de Abya Yala, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Festival Internacional de Cine Drets Humans, Periódico, 2003 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Festival Internacional de Cine y Formación en Derechos Humanos de las Personas Migrantes, 2010 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Festival Internacional de Cine y Video de Derechos Humanos, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Festival Internacional de Cine y Video de Derechos Humanos, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Festival Internacional de Cine y Video de Derechos Humanos, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Festival Internacional de Cine y Video de los Pueblos Indígenas, Chile, 2004-2006 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Festival Internacional de Cine y Video de los Pueblos Indígenas, Chile - Catalog, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Festival Internacional de Cinema e Vidéo de Famalicão, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Festival Internacional de Video Documental, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Festival International du Film d'Amiens, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Film Festival of Douarnenez, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Film Screenings - Flyers, 1998-2010 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - "Films from the Chiapas Media Project and Guest Speaker Aasia Mohammad Castañeda" - Screening Poster, Communication Arts Cinematheque, Ramapo College, NJ, Undated (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Finger Lakes Environmental Film Festival, 2008 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Finger Lakes Environmental Film Festival, 2009 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - First Nations Native American Film and Video Festival, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - First Peoples' Festival (Présence Autochtone), Québec, 2001-2002 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - First Peoples' Festival (Présence Autochtone), Montréal, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - First Peoples' Festival (Présence Autochtone), Montréal, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - First Peoples' Festival (Présence Autochtone), Montréal, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - First Peoples' Festival (Présence Autochtone), Montréal, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - First Peoples' Festival (Présence Autochtone), Montréal, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - First Peoples' Festival (Présence Autochtone), Montréal, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - First Peoples' Festival (Présence Autochtone), Montréal, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - First Peoples' Festival (Présence Autochtone), Montréal, 2006 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - First Peoples' Festival (Présence Autochtone), Montréal, 2009 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - First Peoples' Festival (Présence Autochtone) - Press, Le Devoir, June 4, 2006 (Box Shared Tamiment 069, Folder 17)
  - FORUMDOC.BH, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Geografías Suaves Regional Festival, Mérida, Yucatán, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Geografías Suaves Regional Festival, circa 2004 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Geographical Imaginaries and Hispanic Film Cinemateca, 2009 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Global Visions Festival, Edmonton - Program, 1999 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Gouel ar Filmoù Festival de Cinéma de Douarnenez, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Green Vision Film Festival, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Green Vision Film Festival - Diploma, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Human Rights in Latin America and the Caribbean - Screening Poster, Rutgers University, NJ, 2009 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - imagineNATIVE Aboriginal Media Arts Festival, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - imagineNATIVE Aboriginal Media Arts Festival, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - imagineNATIVE Aboriginal Media Arts Festival, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - imagineNATIVE Aboriginal Media Arts Festival, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - imagineNATIVE Aboriginal Media Arts Festival, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Indigenous Mexico Film Festival, Chicago, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Inventa un Film, Lenola, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Kansas City Filmmakers Jubilee, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Living Juarez Screening Poster, University of Texas-Pan American, Edinburg, TX, Undated (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Los Angeles Freewaves Festival, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Maine International Film Festival, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Margaret Mead Film and Video Festival, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - México Indígena Film Festival - Poster, Chicago, US, 2006-2007 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Monterey Bay Film Fest, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Muestra de Cine y Cooperación, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Muestra de foto-cine y cooperación, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Museum of Modern Art Calendar, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Museum of Modern Art Festival of Non-Fiction Films, New York City, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Museum of Modern Art - Film and Media Exhibitions, December, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Native American Film and Video Festival, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Native American Film and Video Festival, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Native American Film and Video Festival, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Native American Film and Video Festival, 2009 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Native Spirit Festival - Screening Program, The Latin American Association, London, UK, June 4-9, 2007 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Nunavik First Peoples' Festival, Montréal, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - "Of Earth and Sky" Film Screening, American Museum of Natural History, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Ojo del Condor Tour - Correspondence, Schedules, and Flyers, 2001-2002; cuid36503
    - Paper Documents (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Electronic Records, TW_TAM_774_ER_5
  - Open Cinema Film Festival, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - The Other America Film Festival, San Antonio, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Panorama of Ecological Films, Greece, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Paper Tiger TV NYC Schedule, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Paying the Price Screening and Discussion Flyer, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Primer Encuentro de Estudios Visuales, Peru, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Puntos de Vista: Viewpoints from Chiapas and Guerrero - Screening Poster, the Film and Video Center of the NMAI, 2002 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Raíz de la Imagen Festival Internacional de Cine y Video de los Pueblos Indígenas, Oaxaca, Mexico, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Raíz de la Imagen Festival Internacional de Cine y Video de los Pueblos Indígenas, Oaxaca, Mexico - Catalog, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - "Refocusing Chiapas" - Screening Poster, Lebron-Wiggins-Pran Cultural Center, Hampshire College, NH, Undated (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Rural Route Film Festival, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Sámi Film Festival, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - San Diego Latino Film Festival, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Silence of the Zapatistas Screening Advertisement, Salinas Weekly, May, 2001 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Sin Fronteras Film Festival, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Sundance Film Festival, 2000-2001 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Swarthmore College Screening Flyer, circa 2000 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Taiwan International Documentary Festival, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Taller Internacional Sobre Comunicacion y Desarrollo, 2004-2005 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Taos Talking Picture Festival, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Taos Talking Picture Festival, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Toronto International Environmental Film and Video Festival, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - TV or Not TV: Celebration of Experimental Media Arts, Los Angeles, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - txostena, Spain, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - United Nations Association Film Festival, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - United States Tour 1999 - Corresopondence, Contracts, Receipts (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - United States Tour 2000 - Correspondence (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - United States Tour 2001 - Itineraries (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - United States Tour 2002 - Itineraries and Correspondence (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - United States Tour 2003 - Correspondence (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - University Film Screening Contracts, 2005-2006 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Vermont International Film Festival, Burlington, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - "Video Series: Puntos de Vista / Viewpoints from Chiapas and Guerrero," - Screening Announcement, Smithsonian National Museum of the American Indian New York Times, November 1, 2002 (Box Shared Tamiment 069, Folder 18)
  - Viva México: A Retrospective of Mexican Cinema, Florida, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Voices from the Waters Film Festival, 2009 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Wild and Scenic Environmental Film Festival, Nevada City, CA - Program, 2004 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Wild Spaces Environmental Film Festival, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Winnipeg Aboriginal Film and Video Festival, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - WorldFest Houston - Defending the Forests: The Struggle of the Campesino Environmentalists of Guerrero Gold Special Jury Award, 2002 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - WorldFest Houston - Reclaiming Justice: Guerrero's Indigenous Community Police Silver Award, 2003 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - X Festival Internacional de Documentales, Santiago de Cuba, 2009 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - XicanIndie Filmmakers' Fest, Denver, Colorado, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 22)
- Series III. Community Organizing, 1996-2011; 2.5 Linear Feet in 5 manuscript boxes
  This Series contains documents pertaining to the community organizing work of Chiapas Media Project, including workshops and speaking engagements, regional media centers, and youth media delegations. It also includes administrative documentation related to the Cuentos Foundation, Promedios offices in Chicago and Mexico, fundraising activities, grant applications, and budgets and expenses.
  - Aasia Mohammad Castaneda and the Chiapas Media Project - Event Poster Pennsylvania State University, Harrisburg, PA, March 21, 2007 (Box 16, Folder 1)